Fatlum Maliqi

Ferizaj, Republic of Kosovo • +383 43 842 249 hello@fatlummaliqi.com • fatlummaliqi.com

Summary

An exponentially growing software developer with 2+ years of successful experience working at a leading internet services company in Central Europe

Core competences

Problem Solving • Distributed Systems • RESTful Sense • Caching • Event Streaming • Relational databases • Docker

Professional history

Gjirafa Inc • Software developer

June 2024 - Present

Gjirafa Inc · Back-end developer

April 2023 - June 2024

- Developed and maintained server-side components
- Delivered scalable and secure back-end systems
- Wrote clean, efficient and well-documented code

Starlabs • Back-end developer intern

Mars 2022 - April 2022

- Developed features on existing MVC web application
- Participated in quality assurance and automated testing process

Educational history

Universum International College

Graduated with a bachelor's degree in Computer Science

Life from Gjirafa

Graduated with a certificate in non-formal training